Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 21, Folder: 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Training Course - Machine Shop, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Strike Material, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: The Committee to Aid Bell Workers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
    By Richard Lipsitz. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Indirect Job Specification and Labor Grades, Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Box: 21, Folder: 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Productive Job Rating Specification, Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Box: 21, Folder: 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Box: 21, Folder: 5 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: You and Bell Aircraft, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 501 United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: You're a war worker now!, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Employees' Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Functional Chart, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Current Positions Available, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Executive Organization, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Quarter Century Club, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The Challenge of the New Frontier, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Merit Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Educational Matching Program, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Rendezvous; Vol. 1 No. 3, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Let's Look at Your Future, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Agreement between Bell and Niagara Frontier Technical Assoc. Local 205 American Federation of Technical Engineers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Your Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Agreement between Bell and International Union, UAW-CIO, Local 999, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 501, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 501, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Retirement Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Employees Stock Savings Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 22: Agreement between Bell and United Plant Guard Workers of America, Local 501, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 23: Your Group Insurance Plan - Hourly, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 24: agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Your Group Insurance Plan - Non-Hourly, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Letter re. Child Labor Recruitment, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
    By John Meade. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Boy Power Recruiting Poster, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Box: 21, Folder: 6 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Personnel Manual, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Box: 21, Folder: 7 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Recent Developments in Union Activities in Cleveland Department Stores, Publication (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Box: 21, Folder: 8 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Rules and Rates of Pay for Firemen and Hostlers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Story of the Railroad that Grew Up with the United States, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
    By Carroll Bateman. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 9 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Facts and Figures, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: A Special Chemistry, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Organization Chart, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Box: 21, Folder: 10 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Report of Conferences on Foreman Training, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Box: 21, Folder: 11 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Published Papers and Articles, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Abstracts of Policies, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Published Papers and Articles, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Salary Administration Office, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Science in the Service of Mankind, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
    By George A.W. Boehm and Alex Groner. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Directory, Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Box: 21, Folder: 12 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Box: 21, Folder: 13 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Benefits for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Retirement Income Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Retirement Income Plan for Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Benefits for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Handbook, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Marketing Report; Vol. 8 No. 6, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: The Beechcrafter; Vol. 32 No. 16, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: The Story of Beechcraft, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Box: 21, Folder: 14 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Shop Rules, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Box: 21, Folder: 15 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Appendix; Exhibits with Statement by George Romney to the Senate War Investigating Committee on Manpower Problems, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Automotive Practices with Respect to Foremen; Study No. 1-5, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Automotive Management Spokesmen want new labor policy, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Conclusions and General Recommendations of the Panel of the National War Labor Board in Certain Disputes involving Supervisors, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Foreman Unionization, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
    By C.W. Eliason. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Manpower Problem-What it really is, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: 4 out of 5 Veterans Barred from Jobs in Automotive Industry, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Manpower Reports, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Manpower Report No. 34, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Automotive Council to Dissolve October 1, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Box: 21, Folder: 16 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: 1950 Labor Contracts, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Report on Wages paid to Salaried Workers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
    By M.M. Ransier. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Registered Nurses Rates of Pay; Doctor Service Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Report on Rates of Pay for Productive Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Survey of Rates of Pay, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Report on Rates of Pay for Engineering, Toolroom and Laboratory Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Report on Female Bench Inspection Rate of Pay, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Report on Punch Press Operators' rates of pay, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 9: Report on Various Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Report on Various Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 11: Report on Rates of Pay for Certain Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Report on Rates of Pay for Certain Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 13: Registered Nurses Rates of Pay, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: Survey of Rates of Pay to Salaried Workers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Report on Rates of Pay for Boiler Operations, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 16: Report on Rates of Pay for Plant Protection Men, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 17: Report on Rates of Pay for Drill Press and Taping and Reaming Operators, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 18: Report on Rates of Pay for Certain Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 19: Report on Rates of Pay for Certain Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 20: Report on Rates of Pay for Industrially Registered Nurses, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 21: Report on Rates of Pay for Certain Classifications of Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 22: Report on Rates of Pay for Hourly Rated Productive Foremen, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 23: Controlled Materials Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Item 24: Grievance Procedure in Parts Plants, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Box: 21, Folder: 17 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Company Plan, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
    By G.L. Avery. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Letter to the Workmen, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
    By L.A. Phelps. Item is in English.
- Box: 21, Folder: 18 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Report on Foremanship Conference, Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Box: 21, Folder: 19 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Reducing Labor Costs, Publication (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Box: 21, Folder: 20 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: 1879-1979, Publication (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Account Executive Training Program, Publication (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Box: 22, Folder: 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Grade Rate Chart, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Bell and Local 501 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Supplement to Agreement Dated Feb 9, 1940, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Bell and Local 501 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Bell and Local 501 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Bell and Local 501 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America - 2 Copies, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Bell and Amalgamated Union UAW-CIO Local 516, Inspectors' Unit, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Bell and Local 516 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Agreement between Bell and Local 516 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Agreement between Bell and Local 516 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Agreement between Bell and Local 516 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Agreement between Bell and Local 10 UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Agreement between Bell and Local 513 UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Agreement between Bell and Lodge 1638 of the International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Agreement between Bell and Local 501 International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Agreement between Bell and Production Engineering Technical Assoc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Agreement between Bell and Local Union 516, Timekeepers Unit, UAW-CIO and The International Union United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Brief of Arbitrator's Decision - Discharge of V. Copeland and J. Mastartonio, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Letter to G. Baldwin re. Request for Information, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Interview of P.M. Grezelle, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Medical Record, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Plane Assembly Unit Adopts 54 Hour Week, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Written Grievance, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Report of Disciplinary Action, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Employee Rating Cards, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Job Analysis Questionnaire, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    By Leston P. Faneuf. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Employee Patent and Production Improvement Compensation, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Indirect Job Specification and Labor Grades, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Box: 22, Folder: 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: NEWS; Vol. 4 No.1, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Why Join Us?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: What is a Bell and Howell?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Policy Manual, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Sharing the Profits You Help Produce, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: It's a Fifty-Fifty Deal, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Box: 22, Folder: 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Policy Manual, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Protection for You, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Organization Charts, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Retirement Trust, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Box: 22, Folder: 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Glossary of Telephonese, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Birth and Babyhood of the Telephone, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Research and Development in the Bell System, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The Magic CrystalHow the Transistor Revolutionized electronics, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By Dr. M. Brotherton. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Important Features of Bell System savings plan for salaried employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Transfer Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Telephone Story Board, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Conference Notes; Vol. 29 No. 3, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Put on Your Thinking Cap-Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Supervisor's Guide in Management-Union Relations, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Box: 22, Folder: 5 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Non-Management Performance Appraisal Summary, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Safety Training Lesson, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Secrecy of Communications and Protection of Company Property, Records and Services, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Washington's Telephone History and Growth, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Secrecy of Communications and Protection of Company Property, Records and Services, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Basic Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The Extraordinary Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The Extraordinary Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: The Basic Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Highlights of Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Mobility Application Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Box: 22, Folder: 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Your Pension and Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Your Medical Expense Protection Plans, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Basic and Supplementary Group Life Insurance Plans, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Savings Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Special Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Basic Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: You'll Be Proud to be a Pioneer, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Bulletin, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Telenews; Vol. 24 No 21, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Memorandum re. Appraisal of Non-Management Employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Special Information Bulletin re. Transfer Plan Revisions Apr 15, 1975, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Intradepartmental geographical transfer plan for non-management employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: The Why Program, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Manager's Digest No 73-2, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Employment Forms, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Public Affairs Bulletin, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Manager's Digest No 73-19, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Memo re. Computing Overtime Pay, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Report of Employee Complaint or Grievance, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Memo re. Treating Sub-Standard Performance and Conduct, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Safety Assurance Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Box: 22, Folder: 7 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Basic Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Safety Assurance Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Company Organization, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Induction and Orientation of New Employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Discussion Record, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: The Telephone in Maryland, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Maryland Telephone Chronology, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Box: 22, Folder: 8 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Supervisory Guidelines for Non-Management Appraisals, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Box: 22, Folder: 9 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: For Your Benefit, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: History of the Indiana Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Maternity Payment Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Long Term Disability Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Summary Plan Description, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Summary of Bell System Savings Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Summary Plan for Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: New and Improved Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: A Guide to Employee Evaluation, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Dental Expense Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Long Term Disability Plan for Non-Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Employee Transfer Reimbursement Summary, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: General Instruction No. 5, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: General Adjustment Bureau, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Box: 22, Folder: 10 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Health Information for Supervisory Personnel, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Facts about Your Retirement, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Management Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Background and Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Box: 22, Folder: 11 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: After College, What?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: About US, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Management Program Special Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Box: 22, Folder: 12 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Looking for a Job with a Challenge, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Wondering about tomorrow?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: The Bell System in New Jersey, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Ayudas Para Conseguir tu Primer Empleo - Spanish, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Helpful Hints for Getting your First Job, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Call me mister, too!, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Report to Management; Vol. 6 No. 21, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: A Capsule History of the Bell System, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Report to Management; Vol. 6 No. 8, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Organizational Evolution, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Welcome to NJ Bell, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Box: 22, Folder: 13 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Organizational Chart, Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Box: 22, Folder: 14 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Better Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Group Life Insurance Program, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Dental Expense Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Answer Book - Scholarships, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Transfer and Upgrading Plan for Non-Management Jobs, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Box: 22, Folder: 15 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Better Benefits for You and Your Family, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    By Ohio Bell Telephone Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Summary of the Group Life Insurance Program, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Summary of the Plan for Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Answer Book to Questions on th Ohio Bell Merit Scholarships for Employees' Children, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Transfer and upgrading Plan for Non-Management Jobs, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Dental Expense Plan for You and Your Family, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)